import "Catalog/catalog.css";


// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/es.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['á', 'é', 'í', 'ñ', 'ó', 'ú', 'ü' ,'Á', 'É', 'Í', 'Ñ', 'Ó', 'Ú', 'Ü'],
}


export var cards = {
  '0': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Zero',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'cero'
  },
  '1': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'One',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'uno'
  },
  '2': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Two',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'dos'
  },
  '3': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Three',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'tres'
  },
  '4': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Four',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'cuatro'
  },
  '5': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Five',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'cinco'
  },
  '6': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Six',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'seis'
  },
  '7': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Seven',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'siete'
  },
  '8': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Eight',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'ocho'
  },
  '9': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Nine',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'nueve'
  },
  '10': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Ten',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'diez'
  },
  '11': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Eleven',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'once'
  },
  '12': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Twelve',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'doce'
  },
  '13': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Thirteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'trece'
  },
  '14': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Fourteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'catorce'
  },
  '15': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Fifteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'quince'
  },
  '16': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Sixteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'dieciséis'
  },
  '17': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Seventeen',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'diecisiete'
  },
  '18': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Eighteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'dieciocho'
  },
  '19': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Nineteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in Spanish?',
    answer: 'diecinueve'
  },

};